Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session three of unit four it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your unit four assessment
booklet and scroll down to section
three, you will see there are five
learning objectives, and there are
five questions which you will answer
to fulfill those learning objectives.
So if we scroll down to question
one, it's asking you to explain why
perimeter access control is important.
So thinking about organisations
and businesses and premises,
why is it important?
What is perimeter access control?
What is it there to achieve?
So why it is important
to have it in place.
For question two, it's asking you to
give three examples of when checks and
challenges on a premises may be needed.
So thinking about access controls to
premises, specific areas, information.
Why are those checks and challenges...
why would they be needed?
If you can give three examples for that.
Then for question three, it's asking
you to identify the possible threats
to a business presented by the use of
the following, and there's a note here
and this is important, so there are
four areas that you need to look at:
personal devices, removable devices,
hardware, network and infrascructure.
So for the network and infrastructure,
you need to include threats
presented by open wifi and routers.
So when we talk about open
wifi, that's wifi that isn't
protected so anybody can log on.
So you could be in a restaurant or a
cafe and you're using open wifi, somebody
else is using the open wifi, what are
the potential threats that that poses?
Again for routers as well.
If you're using the same information
or people have access, everybody has
access, to these pieces of equipment
or ways of communicating, what
are the threats that that poses?
Then for question four, it's asking
me to give examples of possible
threats presented by remote working.
So since the pandemic, remote working
has become a fact of life, whereas
previously you would go into an
office, office building or a shop or
wherever you were working and there
was likely to be security policies
in place and various factors that
would be there already set up.
So what are the threats that are
being presented by remote work?
So  what are the changes?
How is it impacting and
increasing the possible threats
to information and cyber security?
If you can give three examples for that.
And then for question five,
it's asking you to describe best
practice which can help to minimize
physical threats to cyber security.
So we're talking about physical threats.
So this isn't security in
relation to your computer.
This is security...
this is physical threats.
So what are the practices that
you can have in place to ensure
that physical security is in
place and everything is protected?
So once you've done that, it's time
to review the whole of the assessment.
Have a look at all of your responses,
make sure you're happy with everything,
proofread through your work, carry
out a spelling and grammar check.
Once you're happy with that, you can
then save the unit four assessment
booklet and send it off to your tutor
for assessment and move on to unit five.